[{
   "question": [
        {
            "answer" : "answer what",
            "hint" : "hint what",
            "prompt" : "what?"

        },
        {
            "answer" : "answer why",
            "hint" : "hint why",
            "prompt" : "why??" 
        },
        {
            "answer" : "answer when",
            "hint" : "hint when",
            "prompt" : "when ?"  
        },
        {
            "answer" : "answer who",
            "hint" : "hint who",
            "prompt" : "who ?"  
        },
        {
            "answer" : "answer how",
            "hint" : "hint how",
            "prompt" : "how ?"  
        }
    ],
    "title" : "basic question"
},
{
    "question": [
         {
             "answer" : "answer what IOS",
             "hint" : "hint what IOS",
             "prompt" : "what IOS?"
 
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer why IOS",
             "hint" : "hint why IOS",
             "prompt" : "why IOS?" 
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer when IOS",
             "hint" : "hint when IOS",
             "prompt" : "when IOS?"  
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer who IOS",
             "hint" : "hint who IOS",
             "prompt" : "who IOS?"  
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer how IOS",
             "hint" : "hint how IOS",
             "prompt" : "how IOS ?"  
         }
     ],
     "title" : "IOS question"
 },
 {
    "question": [
         {
             "answer" : "answer what swift",
             "hint" : "hint what swift",
             "prompt" : "what swift?"
 
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer why swift",
             "hint" : "hint why swift",
             "prompt" : "why swift?" 
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer when swift",
             "hint" : "hint when swift",
             "prompt" : "when swift?"  
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer who swift",
             "hint" : "hint who swift",
             "prompt" : "who swift?"  
         },
         {
             "answer" : "answer how swift",
             "hint" : "hint how swift",
             "prompt" : "how swift ?"  
         }
     ],
     "title" : "Swift question"
 }
]